import '../../presentation/widget/quiz_questions_widget.dart';

Map<String, dynamic> histopathQuestions = {
  'Amatuer': <QuizQuestionsWidget>[],
  'Easy': <QuizQuestionsWidget>[
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the primary purpose of tissue fixation in histopathology?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'To enhance tissue sectioning',
        'To preserve cellular structure',
        'To improve staining intensity',
        'To remove excess water from tissues',
      ],
      correctOption: 'To preserve cellular structure',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following fixatives is commonly used to preserve tissue morphology in histopathology?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ethanol',
        'Formalin',
        'Acetic acid',
        'Xylene',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Formalin',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the optimal duration for tissue fixation in formalin before processing for embedding?',
      quizOptions: const [
        '24 hours',
        '48 hours',
        '72 hours',
        '96 hours',
      ],
      correctOption: '24 hours',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which embedding medium is most commonly used in routine histopathology?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Paraffin wax',
        'Resin',
        'Gelatin',
        'Agarose',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Paraffin wax',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the primary purpose of embedding tissue specimens in paraffin wax?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'To improve tissue staining',
        'To enhance tissue sectioning',
        'To preserve tissue morphology',
        'To dehydrate tissues',
      ],
      correctOption: 'To enhance tissue sectioning',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the ideal thickness for tissue sections in routine histopathology slides?',
      quizOptions: const [
        '5-10 micrometers',
        '20-30 micrometers',
        '50-100 micrometers',
        '200-300 micrometers',
      ],
      correctOption: '5-10 micrometers',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which staining technique is commonly used to differentiate between cell nuclei and cytoplasmic structures in histopathology?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Hematoxylin and Eosin (H&E) stain',
        'Masson\'s Trichrome stain',
        'Periodic Acid-Schiff (PAS) stain',
        'Ziehl-Neelsen stain',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Hematoxylin and Eosin (H&E) stain',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What component of tissue does Hematoxylin primarily stain in histopathology?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Nuclei',
        'Cytoplasm',
        'Collagen fibers',
        'Red blood cells',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Nuclei',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a common counterstain used in histopathology staining procedures?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Hematoxylin',
        'Eosin',
        'Safranin',
        'Alcian blue',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Eosin',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which staining technique is commonly used to visualize collagen fibers in histopathology?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Masson\'s Trichrome stain',
        'Periodic Acid-Schiff (PAS) stain',
        'Giemsa stain',
        'Wright-Giemsa stain',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Masson\'s Trichrome stain',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'In histopathology, what are common criteria for accepting tissue specimens for processing?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Presence of necrotic tissue',
        'Insufficient labeling on the container',
        'Inadequate fixation',
        'Proper orientation and adequate size',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Proper orientation and adequate size',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a common reason for rejecting tissue specimens in histopathology?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Proper labeling',
        'Presence of air bubbles in fixative',
        'Clear demarcation of tissue edges',
        'Tissue drying during transport',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Presence of air bubbles in fixative',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the primary purpose of using a cryostat in histopathology?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Tissue fixation',
        'Tissue sectioning at low temperatures',
        'Tissue embedding',
        'Tissue staining',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Tissue sectioning at low temperatures',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following tissues is commonly sectioned using a cryostat in histopathology?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Paraffin-embedded tissues',
        'Formalin-fixed tissues',
        'Fresh frozen tissues',
        'Resin-embedded tissues',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Fresh frozen tissues',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the primary advantage of using a cryostat for tissue sectioning?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Improved tissue morphology',
        'Enhanced tissue staining',
        'Rapid tissue processing',
        'Preservation of tissue antigens',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Preservation of tissue antigens',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'In histopathology, what is the purpose of mounting tissue sections on slides?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'To enhance tissue morphology',
        'To improve tissue sectioning',
        'To prevent tissue dehydration',
        'To facilitate microscopic examination',
      ],
      correctOption: 'To facilitate microscopic examination',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following mounting media is commonly used to cover tissue sections on slides in histopathology?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Xylene',
        'Water',
        'DPX (Dibutyl Phthalate Xylene)',
        'Ethanol',
      ],
      correctOption: 'DPX (Dibutyl Phthalate Xylene)',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the primary purpose of using a coverslip when mounting tissue sections on slides?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'To prevent tissue shrinkage',
        'To enhance tissue staining',
        'To protect tissue sections during storage',
        'To flatten tissue sections for microscopic examination',
      ],
      correctOption: 'To flatten tissue sections for microscopic examination',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a common issue associated with inadequate mounting of tissue sections on slides?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Loss of tissue antigens',
        'Enhanced tissue staining',
        'Improved tissue sectioning',
        'Reduced tissue shrinkage',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Loss of tissue antigens',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the optimal drying time for mounted tissue sections on slides before microscopic examination?',
      quizOptions: const [
        '5-10 minutes',
        '20-30 minutes',
        '1-2 hours',
        'Overnight',
      ],
      correctOption: '1-2 hours',
    ),
  ],
  'Hard': <QuizQuestionsWidget>[
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'In immunohistochemistry (IHC), what is the primary purpose of using antigen retrieval techniques?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'To enhance tissue fixation',
        'To improve tissue sectioning',
        'To unmask epitopes for antibody binding',
        'To prevent tissue dehydration',
      ],
      correctOption: 'To unmask epitopes for antibody binding',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a commonly used method for antigen retrieval in IHC?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Freezing tissue sections',
        'Microwave heating',
        'Adding surfactants to staining solutions',
        'Using cryostat sections',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Microwave heating',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the primary purpose of blocking steps in immunohistochemistry (IHC)?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'To prevent tissue autofluorescence',
        'To reduce non-specific antibody binding',
        'To enhance antigen retrieval',
        'To improve tissue morphology',
      ],
      correctOption: 'To reduce non-specific antibody binding',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a commonly used detection method in IHC for visualizing antigen-antibody complexes?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Hematoxylin and Eosin (H&E) staining',
        'Direct visualization under a microscope',
        'Enzyme-linked immunosorbent assay (ELISA)',
        'Chromogenic or fluorescent labels',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Chromogenic or fluorescent labels',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the primary advantage of using chromogenic labels in IHC detection?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'High sensitivity',
        'Real-time visualization',
        'Permanent staining',
        'Multiplexing capabilities',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Permanent staining',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is NOT a commonly used enzyme in enzyme-based detection methods in IHC?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Horseradish peroxidase (HRP)',
        'Alkaline phosphatase (AP)',
        'Glucose oxidase',
        'β-galactosidase',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Glucose oxidase',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the primary purpose of using in situ hybridization (ISH) techniques in histopathology?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'To detect DNA mutations',
        'To visualize mRNA expression patterns',
        'To enhance tissue fixation',
        'To improve tissue sectioning',
      ],
      correctOption: 'To visualize mRNA expression patterns',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a commonly used probe in ISH for detecting specific nucleic acid sequences?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Antibody',
        'Fluorescent dye',
        'Complementary DNA or RNA probe',
        'Enzyme substrate',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Complementary DNA or RNA probe',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the primary advantage of using fluorescence-based ISH detection methods?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'High specificity',
        'Permanent staining',
        'Real-time visualization',
        'Multiplexing capabilities',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Real-time visualization',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a commonly used counterstain in fluorescence-based ISH?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Hematoxylin',
        'Eosin',
        'DAPI (4\',6-diamidino-2-phenylindole)',
        'Safranin',
      ],
      correctOption: 'DAPI (4\',6-diamidino-2-phenylindole)',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the primary function of an amplification step in ISH techniques?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'To improve tissue fixation',
        'To enhance staining intensity',
        'To reduce non-specific binding',
        'To improve tissue sectioning',
      ],
      correctOption: 'To enhance staining intensity',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a common application of immunohistochemistry (IHC) in clinical pathology?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Determining tissue morphology',
        'Assessing tissue hydration status',
        'Detecting tumor markers',
        'Identifying tissue artifacts',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Detecting tumor markers',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the primary purpose of performing validation studies in immunohistochemistry (IHC)?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'To assess tissue hydration status',
        'To determine tissue morphology',
        'To evaluate assay performance and reliability',
        'To identify tissue artifacts',
      ],
      correctOption: 'To evaluate assay performance and reliability',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a common biomarker detected using immunohistochemistry (IHC) in breast cancer?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'ER (Estrogen Receptor)',
        'PSA (Prostate-Specific Antigen)',
        'AFP (Alpha-Fetoprotein)',
        'CA-125 (Cancer Antigen 125)',
      ],
      correctOption: 'ER (Estrogen Receptor)',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which enzyme is commonly used for chromogenic detection in immunohistochemistry (IHC)?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Alkaline phosphatase (AP)',
        'Glucose oxidase',
        'β-galactosidase',
        'Horseradish peroxidase (HRP)',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Horseradish peroxidase (HRP)',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the primary advantage of using horseradish peroxidase (HRP) in immunohistochemistry (IHC)?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'High sensitivity',
        'Real-time visualization',
        'Permanent staining',
        'Multiplexing capabilities',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Permanent staining',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a common application of immunohistochemistry (IHC) in neuropathology?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Detection of neurodegenerative diseases',
        'Assessment of cardiac function',
        'Identification of liver enzymes',
        'Evaluation of renal function',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Detection of neurodegenerative diseases',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a commonly used detection method in fluorescence-based in situ hybridization (ISH)?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Hematoxylin and Eosin (H&E) staining',
        'Direct visualization under a microscope',
        'Enzymatic chromogenic reactions',
        'Fluorescent labels',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Fluorescent labels',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'What is the primary purpose of using a probe in in situ hybridization (ISH) techniques?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'To visualize tissue morphology',
        'To detect specific nucleic acid sequences',
        'To enhance staining intensity',
        'To improve tissue fixation',
      ],
      correctOption: 'To detect specific nucleic acid sequences',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Which of the following is a common application of in situ hybridization (ISH) in cancer research?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Detection of protein expression patterns',
        'Identification of DNA mutations',
        'Assessment of mRNA levels',
        'Evaluation of tissue hydration status',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Assessment of mRNA levels',
    ),
  ],
  'Professional': <QuizQuestionsWidget>[
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A histopathology laboratory receives tissue specimens for processing. Upon examination, it is noted that some specimens lack proper labeling, with only patient names and no additional identifiers. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Proceed with processing the specimens as they are labeled with patient names.',
        'Contact the referring physician to obtain additional patient identifiers.',
        'Disregard the specimens with incomplete labeling and move on to the next batch.',
        'Assume the specimens belong to the patients whose names are provided and process them accordingly.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Contact the referring physician to obtain additional patient identifiers.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'During routine equipment maintenance, it is discovered that the microtome used for sectioning tissue specimens is not cutting sections evenly and is producing inconsistent thicknesses. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Continue using the microtome but increase the speed to compensate for the uneven cutting.',
        'Ignore the issue as long as the sections are usable for diagnosis.',
        'Immediately stop using the microtome and notify the laboratory manager for repair or replacement.',
        'Use manual sectioning techniques until the microtome is repaired.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Immediately stop using the microtome and notify the laboratory manager for repair or replacement.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A histotechnologist notices that the staining intensity of Hematoxylin and Eosin (H&E) stained slides varies from batch to batch, resulting in inconsistent staining quality. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore the staining variation as it does not affect diagnostic accuracy.',
        'Adjust the staining protocol without documenting the changes.',
        'Document the staining variation and troubleshoot the staining process to identify and address the root cause.',
        'Use alternative staining techniques to avoid variations in staining intensity.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Document the staining variation and troubleshoot the staining process to identify and address the root cause.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A histopathology laboratory receives tissue specimens for processing, but some specimens arrive in leaky containers, compromising the integrity of the samples. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Process the leaky specimens first to prevent further damage.',
        'Discard the leaky specimens as they may be contaminated.',
        'Document the condition of the specimens and notify the referring physician for resubmission.',
        'Transfer the specimens to new containers and proceed with processing.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Document the condition of the specimens and notify the referring physician for resubmission.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A histopathology laboratory is experiencing a higher than usual rate of slide mislabeling, leading to potential patient identification errors. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Increase the speed of slide labeling to meet turnaround time targets.',
        'Implement barcode scanning systems for slide labeling to minimize errors.',
        'Ignore the mislabeling issue as it is unavoidable in high-volume laboratories.',
        'Reduce the number of staff involved in slide labeling to minimize errors.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Implement barcode scanning systems for slide labeling to minimize errors.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A laboratory technician is found discussing patient results with colleagues in a public area of the hospital. What actions should be taken to ensure compliance with confidentiality protocols?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore the incident as it is common practice.',
        'Counsel the technician on the importance of patient confidentiality and document the incident.',
        'Transfer the technician to a different department.',
        'Issue a public apology to the affected patients.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Counsel the technician on the importance of patient confidentiality and document the incident.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Several tissue samples received by the laboratory are poorly fixed and show signs of autolysis. What actions should be taken according to quality standards?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Process the samples as usual to avoid delays.',
        'Reject the samples and request new ones from the submitting physician.',
        'Fix the samples again and proceed with processing.',
        'Document the condition of the samples and process them with a note.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Reject the samples and request new ones from the submitting physician.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'The cryostat used for frozen sections is found to be operating at an incorrect temperature, affecting the quality of the sections. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Continue using the cryostat until it is repaired.',
        'Adjust the sectioning technique to compensate for the temperature issue.',
        'Immediately stop using the cryostat and arrange for maintenance and recalibration.',
        'Use manual freezing techniques until the cryostat is fixed.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Immediately stop using the cryostat and arrange for maintenance and recalibration.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'During a routine audit, it is discovered that some staining reagents are past their expiration date. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Use the reagents until new ones are ordered.',
        'Dispose of the expired reagents and use alternative staining methods.',
        'Immediately stop using the expired reagents and reorder fresh supplies.',
        'Dilute the expired reagents to extend their usability.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Immediately stop using the expired reagents and reorder fresh supplies.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'An internal audit reveals that several standard operating procedures (SOPs) have not been updated to reflect recent changes in laboratory practices. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore the issue as the changes are minor.',
        'Immediately update the SOPs and ensure all staff are trained on the new procedures.',
        'Document the changes separately and refer to them when needed.',
        'Continue using the outdated SOPs to maintain consistency.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Immediately update the SOPs and ensure all staff are trained on the new procedures.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A batch of specimens arrives from a remote clinic without proper refrigeration, potentially compromising their integrity. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Process the specimens immediately to prevent further degradation.',
        'Reject the specimens and request new ones with proper transport conditions.',
        'Document the issue and proceed with processing while noting the potential compromise.',
        'Refrigerate the specimens upon arrival and process them later.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Reject the specimens and request new ones with proper transport conditions.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'The paraffin wax used for embedding tissues is found to be of inconsistent quality, affecting the integrity of the tissue blocks. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Continue using the paraffin and adjust the embedding process.',
        'Discard the paraffin and use a different batch.',
        'Mix the inconsistent paraffin with a new batch to even out the quality.',
        'Document the issue and notify the supplier for a replacement.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Document the issue and notify the supplier for a replacement.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A critical biopsy specimen is received with a request for urgent processing, but the laboratory is currently at full capacity. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Process the specimen along with the regular batch to maintain workflow.',
        'Prioritize the urgent specimen and expedite its processing and reporting.',
        'Inform the requesting physician that the specimen will be processed as per the regular schedule.',
        'Delegate the urgent specimen to a different laboratory for quicker processing.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Prioritize the urgent specimen and expedite its processing and reporting.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A new histotechnology technician/scientist has joined the laboratory but has not yet completed the required competency assessment for all laboratory procedures. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Allow the technologist to work independently based on their previous experience.',
        'Assign a mentor to supervise the technologist until competency assessments are complete.',
        'Limit the technologist to administrative tasks until all assessments are completed.',
        'Permit the technologist to perform procedures and review their work retrospectively.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Assign a mentor to supervise the technologist until competency assessments are complete.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A batch of processed slides shows staining artifacts due to a deviation from the standard staining protocol. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore the artifacts and issue the slides for diagnosis.',
        'Reprocess the slides and document the non-conformity.',
        'Notify the pathologist about the artifacts and proceed with the current slides.',
        'Discard the affected slides and start a new batch.',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Reprocess the slides and document the non-conformity.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'The laboratory receives a notification of failing a recent external proficiency testing round for immunohistochemistry. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore the results as a one-time anomaly.',
        'Investigate the cause of the failure and implement corrective actions.',
        'Discontinue the immunohistochemistry testing until further notice.',
        'Repeat the proficiency test immediately without any changes.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Investigate the cause of the failure and implement corrective actions.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A lab technician accidentally sends a patient\'s histopathology report to the wrong physician. What actions should be taken to ensure quality and confidentiality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Ignore the mistake as it was unintentional.',
        'Notify the patient and the correct physician, and implement corrective measures to prevent recurrence.',
        'Delete the report from the records and resend it to the correct physician.',
        'Discipline the technician without informing the patient.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Notify the patient and the correct physician, and implement corrective measures to prevent recurrence.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'The cryostat used for frozen sections is found to be contaminated, potentially compromising the sterility of the samples. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Continue using the cryostat while cleaning it periodically.',
        'Stop using the cryostat immediately, decontaminate it thoroughly, and perform a sterility check.',
        'Use alternative sectioning methods until the cryostat is fully decontaminated.',
        'Increase the frequency of cleaning without stopping its use.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Stop using the cryostat immediately, decontaminate it thoroughly, and perform a sterility check.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'Several tissue sections are found to be of inconsistent thickness, leading to difficulties in interpretation. What actions should be taken to ensure quality in this scenario?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Adjust the microtome settings and re-cut the sections.',
        'Ignore the issue as long as the sections are interpretable.',
        'Document the issue and inform the pathologist of the variability.',
        'Use thicker sections to ensure consistency.',
      ],
      correctOption: 'Adjust the microtome settings and re-cut the sections.',
    ),
    QuizQuestionsWidget(
      markObtain: 0,
      selectedOption: '',
      quizQuestion:
          'A set of biopsy samples arrive without the required clinical history and requisition forms. What actions should be taken according to quality standards?',
      quizOptions: const [
        'Process the samples to avoid delays in diagnosis.',
        'Contact the referring clinic to obtain the necessary documentation before processing.',
        'Discard the samples due to incomplete information.',
        'Document the issue and proceed with the limited information available.',
      ],
      correctOption:
          'Contact the referring clinic to obtain the necessary documentation before processing.',
    ),
  ]
};
